DARSHAN PANCHAL

+64-273793707

panchaldarshan507@gmail.com

inkedin.com/in/darshan-panchal□11668129a

Objective Statement

A serious, focused and career-oriented IT Software Professional with NZQA level 7 qualification. Track record of professional experience in stakeholder management & customer service delivery. Team player with strong work ethics and attention to detail, prompt evaluation, troubleshooting, and ensuring resolution to issues while keeping up with latest IT trends, techniques, and industry best practices. Skilled in resolving software glitches and fixing system errors, sound knowledge of networking protocols, web developer and network environment.

Experience

07/2019 – 02/2020 COMPUTER TECHNICIAN INTERN, N TECH (VADODARA, GUJARAT, INDIA)

- Respond & Resolve to all Technical queries as per the SLA's
- Set up hardware, install and configure software drivers
- Test and implement new software programs for a company
- Installing OS for clients
- Responsible for internet security software updating & Smooth operation
- Provide technical assistance and resolution to stakeholders
- Setting up backup for assets enterprise wide
- Software patching and upgrading for the whole enterprise

03/2019 - 07/2019

CALL CENTER EXECUTIVE, LN ENTERPRISES (VADODARA, GUJARAT, INDIA)

- Maintain operational efficiency through following proper office protocols
- Update database with information guickly and efficiently
- Support customers with any issues
- Provide accurate information to customers

• Respond to all inquiries and requests in a timely manner

Technical Skills

- Hardware Assembly, Maintenance, Peripherals, Printer, Drivers, Troubleshooting
- Microsoft office 365- team, outlook, Servers Active Directory, zoom
- Hyper-V, Oracle VM, Installation of windows server 2016, 2019, windows 10 on VM
- OS- Microsoft windows 7,8,10,11, Android, IOS
- Network: configuration of Router, Switch, Server, LAN and WAN, Putty
- Good knowledge of TCP/IP network, DNS, DHCP, DHCPv6, Routing protocols (OSPF, EIGRP)
- Remote Desktop tool: Team viewer
- Ticketing system sales force (CRM),

Soft Skills

- Excellent Customer-service delivery skills in both written and verbal communication
- Excellent telephone skills
- Good analytical and troubleshooting skills
- Excellent organizational skills
- Ability to vary with different age groups of people
- Keeps abreast of changes in technology

Education

DECEMBER 2021 (6/2020 - 6/2023)

NZQA LEVEL 7 IN SOFTWARE ENGINEEARING

References

Will be furnished upon request.